Women's Studies Program Records UA220
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Women's Studies Program Records
1969 -- 2011
1985 -- 2000
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Women's Center
Women's Studies Program
UA220
6.0 Linear Feet 5 boxes
46 Digital Object(s)
Arrangement
This collection is organized into two series: Program and curriculum development; and Workshops and conferences.
Scope and Contents
This collection contains the Women's Studies Program's curriculum committee notes, program board minutes, faculty committee agendas and minutes, course syllabi and fliers, publications, photographs, and conference materials from 1981-2010. It comprises physical records, audio and video material, and digital records.
Biographical / Historical
The Women's Studies program grew out of the Experimental College in the 1970s and shared many resources with the Women's Center. It officially offered a minor in 1983-1984. In 1985, they organized the first "Beyond the Classroom" forum for students to present their work. Initially there were two committees overseeing the program: the Curriculum Committee which developed the department's curriculum, and the Program Board which oversaw events and program development. Following an external review of the department in 1997, Women's Studies restructured. It consolidated the committees into one Faculty Committee with several sub-committees and was encouraged to break its structural ties with the Women's Center. Beginning in 1999, Women's Studies offered an interdisciplinary major. In 2005, they hosted the first International Women's Day to celebrate the achievements of women. Additionally, they host a yearly Research Colloquium Series that brings in speakers to talk on topics relating to women and gender.
Women's Studies Program, records, 1981-2010. UA220. Tufts University. Digital Collections and Archives. Medford, MA.
Conditions Governing Access
University records are closed for 20 years from the date of their creation. Records older than 20 years that do not pertain to student education, staff and faculty employment and Board of Trustees records are open for research.
Curriculum and Instruction -- Academic Departments and Programs; Curriculum and Instruction -- Teaching Material
- Program and Curriculum Development, 1969 -- 2010; UA220.001; 4.8 Linear Feet; 22 Digital Object(s)
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains Women's Studies publications, agendas and minutes from Curriculum Committee and Program Board, administrative and faculty support files, faculty CVs, course flyers and syllabi, Tufts Women's Studies Newspaper and website. Original order was not apparent when the physical files were received. Efforts were made to keep files grouped in hanging file folders together. Order was imposed chronologically by the function which created the records. Several digital items contain material in both series 1 and series 2. These are primarily back-up files of the entire file structure on the Women's Studies computer. The decision was made to not break apart the original digital structure into the two series since we would lose the original file structure. Refer to the individual records for more details.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged chronologically by topic.
  Conditions Governing Access
  Open for research.
  - Curriculum Committee and Program Board, 1981 -- 2010; UA220.001.001
    - [Women's Studies publications], 1988 -- 1989; UA220.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
    - [Wellesley College Center for Research on Women publications, folder 1 of 2], 1983 -- 1984; UA220.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
    - [Wellesley College Center for Research on Women publications, folder 2 of 2], 1984 -- 1987; UA220.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
    - [Center for Research on Women Publications, Memphis State University], 1986 -- 1989; UA220.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
    - WS: Historical Documents, 1981 -- 1988; UA220.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
    - WS: historical docs., 1987 -- 1988; UA220.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
    - Womens Studies, 1985 -- 1986; UA220.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
    - Valentines, 1987 -- 1988; UA220.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies, 1987 -- 1988; UA220.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
    - WSCC, 1988 -- 1989; UA220.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
    - WSCC, 1989 -- 1990; UA220.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
    - Womens Studies Rev., 1990 -- 1991; UA220.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
    - WSCC, 1991 -- 1992; UA220.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
    - WSCC, 1992 -- 1993; UA220.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
    - W.S. Curriculum Comm., 1993 -- 1994; UA220.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
    - [Course development correspondence], 1992 -- 1994; UA220.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
    - WSCC, 1994 -- 1995; UA220.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
    - WSCC, 1995 -- 1996; UA220.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
    - WSCC, 1996 -- 1997; UA220.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
    - Womens Studies Curriculum Committee 1997-98, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies Curriculum Committee, 1996 -- 1997; UA220.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
    - WS Curriculum Committee 97-8, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
    - Program Board - Past, 1986 -- 1987; UA220.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
    - Program Board 1987-88, 1987 -- 1988; UA220.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
    - WPB, 1988 -- 1989; UA220.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
    - WPB, 1989 -- 1990; UA220.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
    - WPB - Fall 1990-91, 1990 -- 1991; UA220.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
    - W.S. Faculty Disc group, 1991; UA220.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
    - W.S. Fac. Meeting 2/91, 1902 -- 1991; UA220.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
    - WPB, 1991 -- 1992; UA220.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
    - WPB, 1992 -- 1993; UA220.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
    - WPB, 1993 -- 1994; UA220.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
    - WPB, 1994 -- 1995; UA220.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
    - WPB, 1995 -- 1996; UA220.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
    - Womens Studies, 1996 -- 1997; UA220.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
    - Women's Studies, 1996 -- 1997; UA220.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
    - Meeting Minutes 1997-98, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
    - WS, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
    - WS March, 1997; UA220.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
    - WS Committee Members, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
    - WS Board Mtngs, 1998 -- 1999; UA220.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
    - WS Board Meetings, 1999 -- 2000; UA220.001.001.00042 (Box 1)
    - WS Board Mtngs, 1998 -- 2010; UA220.001.001.00043 (Box 1)
    - [Faculty Committee Notes 2005], UA220.001.001.00044 (Box 1)
  - Faculty Administrative Support, 1969 -- 2009; UA220.001.002
    - WS Board Meeting Minutes, 2002 -- 2009; UA220.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
    - WS Board Meeting Handouts, 2002 -- 2003; UA220.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
    - Faculty Committee - History, 1998 -- 2009; UA220.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
    - Committee on the Evaluation of Educational Outcomes, 2007; UA220.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
    - Koppleman Gift to Women's Studies - correspondence, etc., 1991; UA220.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
    - WS, 1990 -- 1991; UA220.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
    - Development Office Records, 1991 -- 1994; UA220.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
    - WS Minor, 1991; UA220.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
    - WS, 1991 -- 1992; UA220.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
    - WS, 1992 -- 1993; UA220.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
    - WS minor records, 1987 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00011
    - WS, 1993 -- 1994; UA220.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
    - [Correspondence draft], 1993; UA220.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
    - WS, 1994 -- 1995; UA220.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
    - WS Brochure rev F94, 1994; UA220.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
    - WS application for undergrad directory, 1995; UA220.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
    - [Womens studies director search], 1994 -- 1995; UA220.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
    - New faculty university general information, 1996 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
    - W faculty letter, 1995; UA220.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
    - WS Structure, 1994 -- 1995; UA220.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
    - Lecture, Intro F97, 1997; UA220.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
    - Memos - general sent, 1996; UA220.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
    - Memos received, 1996; UA220.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
    - [Womens Studies ], 1996; UA220.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
    - WM 72, 1999; UA220.001.002.00025
    - [Administration and Faculty Support 1 of 6], 1996; UA220.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
    - WS & program Board (WSPB) & sub committee general [Administration and Faculty support 2 of 6], 1996; UA220.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
    - Womens curriculum sub-committee [Administration and Faculty Support 3 of 6], 1996; UA220.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
    - Womens studies faculty [Administration and Faculty suppor 4 of 6], 1996 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
    - WS/WP Division of Labour, 1996; UA220.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
    - [Administration and Faculty Support 6 of 6], UA220.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
    - grants - gen info, 1996; UA220.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
    - [Director search application], 1995 -- 1996; UA220.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
    - Class list and student information 190/3/4, 1996 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
    - Women Studies notebook, 1996; UA220.001.002.00035
    - Faculty support of students, 1996 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
    - Womens Studies '95-'96, '96-'97 [binder, front matter, folder 1 of 5], 1995 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies '95-'96, '96-'97, WS Syllabi [binder, folder 2 of 5], 1995 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies '95-'96, '96-'97, WS Curriculum [binder, folder 3 of 5], 1995 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies '95-'96, '96-'97, Let/Forms/Flyers [binder, folder 4 of 5], 1995 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies '95-'96, '96-'97, Miscellaneous [binder, folder 5 of 5], 1995 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
    - External Review, 1997; UA220.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
    - Review, 1997; UA220.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
    - History of [Women's Studies], 1985 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
    - History of WS at Tufts, 1997; UA220.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
    - Rebecca's work, 1995 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
    - mailing to faculty, 1997; UA220.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
    - [Tufts Women's Studies History], 1997; UA220.001.002.00048 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Narrative History External Review, Part I [binder, folder 1 of 5], 1969 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00049 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Narrative History External Review, Part II [binder, folder 2 of 5], 1969 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00050 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Narrative History External Review, Part III [binder, folder 3 of 5], 1969 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00051 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Narrative History External Review, Part IV [binder, folder 4 of 5], 1969 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00052 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Narrative History External Review, Part V [binder, folder 5 of 5], 1969 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00053 (Box 2)
    - WS Year by Year, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.002.00054
      Series 1: Admin/support files, 1997 WS Review Series 2: Beyond the classroom forum submissions 1998
    - [Women's Studies 72, 1998], UA220.001.002.00055 (Box 2)
    - Back-up: Paperport, Misc, Majors, 1998 -- 1999; UA220.001.002.00056
    - Business Notes, 1999; UA220.001.002.00057 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies '97-2001 [binder, folder 1 of 3], 1997 -- 2001; UA220.001.002.00058 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies '97-2001 [binder, folder 2 of 3], 1997 -- 2001; UA220.001.002.00059 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies '97-2001, course related [binder, folder 3 of 3], 1997 -- 2001; UA220.001.002.00060 (Box 2)
    - Annual Report, 1999 -- 2004; UA220.001.002.00061
      Series 1: Annual report 99-00 Series 2: Beyond the classroom participants list (1986-2004)
    - Teacher evaluation analysis, 1999 -- 2000; UA220.001.002.00062
    - Center for Improvement of Teaching, 1999; UA220.001.002.00063
    - End of Year Report, 1999 -- 2000; UA220.001.002.00064
    - [Proposal for major in Women's Studies], 1999; UA220.001.002.00065 (Box 2)
    - WS Major Info - External, 1998 -- 1999; UA220.001.002.00066 (Box 2)
    - Student Support for WS Major, 1998; UA220.001.002.00067 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Major, 1999; UA220.001.002.00068 (Box 2)
    - WS My Documents, 1996 -- 2001; UA220.001.002.00069
      Series 1: Women's Studies website, 97 review, committee meeting agenda and minutes, minor requirements, course lists and fliers, labels Series 2: Beyond the classroom forum, senior project presentations, event fliers
    - My Documents Backup 10-17-07, 1996 -- 2007; UA220.001.002.00070
      Series 1: Alumna lists, course lists and fliers, major/minor requirements and students, faculty lists, committee meeting agendas and minutes (1998-2008), administrative to-do lists, labels, letters, memos, newsletter (Fall 2000-Spring 2005), Women's Studies website Series 2: Beyond the classroom forum 1999-2007 planning and participants, Chinese Women conference 1999, International Women's Day, senior project presentations, event fliers
    - [Institutional Research Senior Survey Results], 2002 -- 2004; UA220.001.002.00071 (Box 2)
    - [Accredidation], 2007 -- 2008; UA220.001.002.00072 (Box 2)
    - WS Faculty and Staff Writing Samples, 1993 -- 1997; UA220.001.002.00073 (Box 2)
    - A-J [Curriculum Vitae WS Faculty & Staff], 1997; UA220.001.002.00074 (Box 2)
    - K-Z [Curriculum Vitae WS Faculty & Staff], 1997; UA220.001.002.00075 (Box 2)
    - WS - CVs, 1997; UA220.001.002.00076 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Curriculum Vitae faculty and staff [binder, folder 1 of 2], 1997; UA220.001.002.00077 (Box 2)
    - Women's Studies Curriculum Vitae Faculty and Staff [binder, folder 2 of 2], 1997; UA220.001.002.00078 (Box 2)
  - Course Syllabi, 1986 -- 2010; UA220.001.003
    - [Course offering flyers], 1986 -- 1991; UA220.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
    - Course Booklets [folder 1 of 2], 1986 -- 2010; UA220.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
    - Course Booklets [folder 2 of 2], 2003 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
    - Course booklet 2000, UA220.001.003.00004
    - Course infor, 1987 -- 1988; UA220.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
    - WS - Information on course offerings - syllabi etc 80s, 1988 -- 1990; UA220.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi Collected in Spring, 1989 -- 1991; UA220.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
    - [Introduction to Women's Studies course], 1986 -- 1992; UA220.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
    - Syllabi 1995-1997 Am. Studies - History, 1992 -- 1997; UA220.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
    - Syllabi 1995-1997 Judaic Studies - WS, 1988 -- 1997; UA220.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
    - WS syllabi, 1993 -- 1996; UA220.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Disk, 1994 -- 1996; UA220.001.003.00012
    - Classes, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
    - [Women's Studies courses], 1994 -- 1998; UA220.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi and course descriptions 1995-1997 [binder, folder 1 of 2], UA220.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi and course description 1995-1997 [binder, folder 2 of 2], UA220.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Minor, 1994 -- 1996; UA220.001.003.00017
    - WS 97-98 program flyers, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
    - Work home work, 1994 -- 1996; UA220.001.003.00019
      Series 1: Spring 1999 courses, logo Series 2: Chinese Women conference 1999, Research Colloquium 1998-11-23
    - Sample Syllabi - global feminisms, 2003; UA220.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
    - Tufts WS 92 - Spring, 2003; UA220.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Arabic [binder, folder 1 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Anthro [binder, folder 2 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Biology [binder, folder 3 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Classics [binder, folder 4 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Comm. Health [binder, folder 5 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Comp. Religion [binder, folder 6 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Drama [binder, folder 7 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Economics [binder, folder 8 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Education [binder, folder 9 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, English [binder, folder 10 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Ex-College [binder, folder 11 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E, Economics [binder, folder 12 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi A-E [binder, back matter, folder 13 of 13], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi F-L, FAH (art history) [binder, folder 1 of 7], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi F-L, French [binder, folder 2 of 7], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi F-L, G.R.A. Lang [binder, folder 3 of 7], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi F-L, History [binder, folder 4 of 7], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi F-L, Italian [binder, folder 5 of 7], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi F-L, Japanese [binder, folder 6 of 7], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi F-L, Judaic Studies [binder, folder 7 of 7], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00041 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi M-Z, Music [binder, folder 1 of 9], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00042 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi M-Z, Philosophy [binder, folder 2 of 9], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00043 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi M-Z, Poli Sci [binder, folder 3 of 9], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00044 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi M-Z, Psychology [binder, folder 4 of 9], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00045 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi M-Z, Russian [binder, folder 5 of 9], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00046 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi M-Z, Sociology [binder, folder 6 of 9], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00047 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi M-Z, Spanish [binder, folder 7 of 9], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00048 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi M-Z, Women's Studies [binder, folder 8 of 9], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00049 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Syllabi M-Z, Graduate Consortium [binder, folder 9 of 9], 1989 -- 2009; UA220.001.003.00050 (Box 3)
    - Women's Studies Internships, 1996; UA220.001.003.00051 (Box 3)
    - Internship Opportunity- center for Women Policy Studies, 1996; UA220.001.003.00052 (Box 3)
    - Internships - Cross Cultural Solutions info, 2001; UA220.001.003.00053 (Box 3)
  - Newsletter and Website, 1987 -- 2009; UA220.001.004
    - Careers and Internships in Women's Studies [binder, folder 1 of 4], 2000 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00001 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Careers and Internships in Women's Studies, Internships [binder, folder 2 of 4], 2000 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00002 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Careers and Internships in Women's Studies, Newsletters [binder, folder 3 of 4], 2000 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00003 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Careers and Internships in Women's Studies, Newsletters [binder, folder 4 of 4], 2000 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00004 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Careers for Women's Studies Majors [binder, front matter, folder 1 of 2], 2000 -- 2009; UA220.001.004.00005 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Careers for Women's Studies Majors [binder, folder 2 of 2], 2000 -- 2009; UA220.001.004.00006 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - WS Grad Programs, 1998 -- 1999; UA220.001.004.00007 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Consortium Grad Research, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.004.00008
    - Women's Studies Programs Graduate, 1997 -- 1998; UA220.001.004.00009 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies Outside of Tufts [binder, front matter, folder 1 of 6], 1999 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00010 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies Outside of Tufts, conferences [binder, folder 2 of 6], 1999 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00011 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies Outside of Tufts, Grant/fellow [binder, folder 3 of 6], 1999 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00012 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies Outside of Tufts, Jobs/Intern [binder, folder 4 of 6], 1999 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00013 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies Outside of Tufts, Misc [binder, folder 5 of 6], 1999 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00014 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies Outside of Tufts, Universities [binder, folder 6 of 6], 1999 -- 2002; UA220.001.004.00015 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - News Clippings 1998- [binder], 1998 -- 2001; UA220.001.004.00016 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - WS Newspaper Clippings, 1999 -- 2000; UA220.001.004.00017 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - WS Tufts Public Relations, UA220.001.004.00018 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - WS Tufts, 1988 -- 1993; UA220.001.004.00019 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies newsletters Tufts, 1994; UA220.001.004.00020 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Tufts WS Newsletter, 1994; UA220.001.004.00021 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - [Women's Studies Tufts Newsletter correspondence], 1993 -- 1994; UA220.001.004.00022 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - [Women's Studies Newsletter], 2002 -- 2003; UA220.001.004.00023 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - WS Newsletter, 2003; UA220.001.004.00024
    - Brochure, 1990 -- 1994; UA220.001.004.00025 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies - Misc, 1993; UA220.001.004.00026 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Back-up Webpages, 1998 -- 1999; UA220.001.004.00027
    - Back-up Workstudy, 1998 -- 1999; UA220.001.004.00028
    - Earth jpg, 2000; UA220.001.004.00029
    - Misc .gif, 2000; UA220.001.004.00030
    - WS webpage, 1998; UA220.001.004.00031 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Add to web page, 1999 -- 2000; UA220.001.004.00032 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - [Women vs. Gender correspondence], 1998; UA220.001.004.00033 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - Women's Studies v. Gender Studies, 2000; UA220.001.004.00034 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - [Jackson Institute for the Study of Women in Cross-Cultural Perspective], UA220.001.004.00035 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - [Women's Studies Flyers], 1992 -- 1997; UA220.001.004.00036 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
    - ESL certificate, 2000; UA220.001.004.00037 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
- Workshops and Conferences, 1984 -- 2011; UA220.002; 2.4 Linear Feet; 24 Digital Object(s)
  This series contains event flyers, correspondence, audio and video recordings of conferences, photographs and planning notes for Beyond the Classroom Forum, International Women's Day, Race and Gender in the Curriculum, and other workshops hosted by the Women's Studies program from 1985-2009. See series 1 scope notes for digital records that may contain material intellectually associated with series 2.
  This series is arranged chronologically.
  - [Women on the Edge of the 21st Century], 1985; UA220.002.005.00001 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Forum, 1986; UA220.002.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - [Beyond the Classroom] Women as oppressors/panel 1 4-11-86, 1904 -- 1986; UA220.002.005.00003 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - [Beyond the Classroom] Women as workers: Never done / panel 2, 4-11-86, 1904 -- 1986; UA220.002.005.00004 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - [Beyond the Classroom] Beyond the Margins: Women and Sexuality / panel 3, 4-11-86, 1904 -- 1986; UA220.002.005.00005 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - Howard Conf, 1986; UA220.002.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Forum, 1987; UA220.002.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - [Women of Many Visions] P. Collins Keynote - Casette 1, 1987; UA220.002.005.00008 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - [Women of Many Visions] Panel 1, Panel 2 - Casette 2, 1987; UA220.002.005.00009 (Box UA220 Shared 1)
  - [Women of Many Visions] Panel 2, Panel 3 - Casette 3, 1987; UA220.002.005.00010 (Box UA220 Shared 1)